

Kirill Elizarov

.Net Developer

PROFILE

Address

Prague, Czech Republic

Phone Number +420 77 99 70 567

Email Address

kiril.elizarov@gmail.com

Date Of Birth

17 August 1990

LinkedIn

Kirill Elizarov

Github kulebyaka

LANGUAGES

Czech

Russian

English

•

Native Tongue

BUZZWORDS

C#, SOLID, agile, Code review,
REST API, .Net Core 3, IOC
Container, NUnit, Entity
Framework, Angular, React,
KendoUI, ASP webforms, Heroku,
Azure, Postgre Sql, Oracle, MS
SQL, TFS, git, Teamcity, Rider, VS,
Resharper, Postman

CERTIFICATIONS / COURSES / HACKATHONS

CCNA Routing and Switching Cisco Systems

January 2010

Angular 2 Basic

February 2019

Systems Design Fundamentals AlgoExpert

React JS and Redux Bootcamp udemy

HACKPRAGUE 2020

Dateio challenge prize

HOBBIES

Game development (Unity), IoT, squash, hiking, skiing

OBJECTIVE

Software engineer with 8 years of experience in developing complex applications in the banking and B2B sectors. I have experience in leading team, developing new products from scratch in a limited timeframe, and long-term support of systems with a large backlog.

SOFT SKILLS

Teamwork / Mentorship

Growth mindset / Adaptability

Leadership / Delegating
Intermediate

Advanced

Advanced

Initiative / Time management

Advanced

WORK EXPERIENCE

First Line Software

Senior .Net Developer

(April 2021 - Present)

Kin and Carta - Around 10 different projects developed for UK and international clients, such as Pizza Hut and National Football League. *Area of responsibility:*

- Implementation of standard Episerver CMS functionality and finetuning (e.g. prioritizing search results on the site) and implementation new features such as a recommendation system based on tags and their order, sceduled job for bulk content generation from RSS feed, etc.
- Presentation of work results to clients
- CI/CD configuring, code reviews

Cleverlance

(August 2017 - March 2021)

.Net Developer

Development of an application for approving corporate credit products. It covers the entire approval workflow: tasks, design and approval of financing, risk analysis, contractual documentation, loan drawdown. *Area of responsibility:*

- Architectural design based on a functional specification
- Incident management
- A consequential migration to new technologies

SKB Kontur

Back end developer, Team leader

(March 2020 - December 2020)

Development of a service for small businesses - **simple ESR (Electronic Sales Registration) cash register**. *Area of responsibility:*

- System design and task delegation
- API development
- Maintenance of technical documentation
- CI/CD configuring

Spring systems, s.r.o.

ASP.NET Developer

(October 2015 - July 2017)

Development and support of a benefit system. Area of responsibility:

- Development of a tree-like task management system with storing the history of changes
- Creating a demo version, prototyping new features

SoftMax

Software Engineer

(December 2013 - August 2014)

Development of a reliable **test management solution**. It includes task management, incident tracking, sprint management *Area of responsibility:*

- Reverse engineering of the data access level of an old project developed in VB6
- Implementation of DAL on .Net
- Development of a data filtering and validation system

EDUCATION

Ural State University

(September 2007 - August 2012)

Bachelor Applied Mathematics